在复制了assets之后，更新Android列表的启动图标，
After copying over the assets, updating the launcher icon
并且给应用程序类添加辅助方法，
in the Android manifest, and adding the Helper methods
我们需要修改
to the Utility class, we need to modify the
DetailFragment还有ForecastAdapter这两个类。在DetailFragment类的onLoadFinished方法里，
DetailFragment and ForecastAdapter classes. In the DetailFragment class, in the
我们从光标读天气条件代码
onLoadFinished method, we read the weather condition code from
然后我们将它传给Utility Helper方法，
the cursor, then we pass it into the Utility
以此获得设置视图的彩色图标
Helper method to get the colored icon for setting
在加载完成方法的详细片段里
onto the image view. In the detail fragment on load
我们从光标阅读天气条件代码。
finish method, we read the weather condition code from the cursor.
然后我们将它传给Utility Helper方法，
Then we pass this into the Utility helper method, to get
然后得到Resource ID的彩色图标，就是为了设置视图。
the Resource ID for the colored icon, in order to set
预测适配器的变化有点棘手，
it onto the Image View. The forecast adapter change is a
因为我们为这个今天的布局使用彩色图标。
little trickier because we want to use the colored icon for the
并且我们想为其他天使用一个灰色图标。
today layout. And we want to use a grey icon for
为了区分他们二者，
the other days. In order to distinguish between the other two,
我们称之为获得给定当前光标位置项目的视图类型。
we call get item view type given the current cursor position.
如果视图类型是今天，那么我们就会从光标出得到天气条件代码
If the view type is today, then we get the weather condition
然后我们从辅助方法里得到彩色图片的ID资源。
code from the cursor. Then we get the resource ID for the
然后我们就把他放到视图上。
colored image from the helper method. And then we set that onto
如果视图类型是回来的某一天，
the image view. If the view type is for a future day, then
那么我们就会从光标出得到天气条件代码
we read the whether condition code from the cursor. Then we pass
然后我们从辅助方法里得到灰色图片的ID资源。
it into the helper method to get the resource ID the gray
然后我们把它发送到图片视图上。
icon and then we send that on to the image view. If
如果我们先前硬编码一个图片到布局里，那么你现在应该删除这些值。
you previously hard coded an image into the layout, then you should remove
否则，在应用程序启动中，他就会
that value now. Otherwise, on app launch, it will load
加载图像占位符并且闪到实际的图标上。
up the placeholder image and then flash to the actual
现在手机用户界面的线框基本上已经
icon. Now that the wire frame implementation for the phone
全部实现了，让我们看看平板电脑的用户界面吧。
UI is pretty much complete, let's look at the tablet UI.